So you live in this neighborhood.
I was just here not long ago.
We're almost there. I'll head off now.
Also,
you don't have to do this next time.
Does what happened today
count as spending the night together?
-Can you stop bringing up spending the night—
-You're back.
I've been waiting for you
at home for a while now.
Have you had
dinner yet?
Hello,
I'm Yoo Taeseok,
a close friend of Yihyun.
Hello.
I'm the one starring
in Director Jung Yihyun's musical,
Kang Jae-on.
Tell me honestly,
what's your relationship with that guy?
There's nothing between us.
Hyung.
What are you thinking about?
What's got you so focused?
You didn't even hear me call you.
Ah...
Well...
Just random thoughts.
I'm Yoo Taeseok, a close friend of Yihyun.
Hah.
A close friend of Yihyun.
Who asked?
Tsk.
Hey.
In your eyes,
how am I?
You?
Well...
Pretty energetic.
Very energetic,
pretty much so.
No, I'm not asking about
things like that.
I'm talking about looks.
My looks.
You... are not my type.
You're not mine either.
What I'm trying to say is
am I that average?
Anyone can tell
there's a stark difference.
With who?
Huh?
Uh... It's nothing.
I'm getting off work.
-See you tomorrow.
-Okay.
[Hongseok]
[Park Seonghyun]
[Shin Yongseok] [Shin Junseop] [Ha Yosep]
[Play Me]
Why is he here?
Could it be that he stayed up all night
working part-time again?
Is it today?
The day we spend the night together.
Answer me.
Right now.
Right here.
Do you want to
spend the night together?
Oh, you're here.
You're here.
Hello.
Ah, you must be the one.
What's going on? Huh?
Did you decide to work together?
Really?
Don't make a fuss.
Hey,
what do you mean make a fuss?
Didn't you watch his performance
and completely fall in love...
What's wrong?
What's wrong? Are you shy?
Is it a secret?
What's wrong?
Then I'll leave too. Please go on.
Wait for me!
Ah...
so cute.
So cute, Jung Yihyun.
How can you let the actor do these things?
It's nothing.
I'm very good at this.
Leave it to me.
I'm touched.
You're so easy to get along with.
Completely opposite to someone.
Speaking of,
your personalities are worlds apart.
How did you become friends?
Did he say... we're friends?
Yes.
He said you two
were really close back in school.
Is that not so?
I need to take a call.
Ah, okay.
Hello?
I heard you told your manager
that we are friends.
You're telling others we are friends,
but why are you still
speaking to me so formally?
After all, we didn't meet as friends.
Let's talk.
Ha...
You are really...
hard to figure out.
Five years ago,
you suddenly turned cold towards me.
When I initiated a conversation,
you ignored me.
You treated me like I was invisible.
There must be a reason, right?
I thought we were close.
Close?
Weren't you just fooling around with me?
Jung Yihyun.
Since he's a celebrity,
I hung out with him a few times,
but he's actually pretty boring.
Jae-on,
please come give me a hand.
Ah, okay.
Now is not the time to argue about this.
Let's rehearse separately for a while.
[Let's rehearse separately for a while.]
[Then when will we see each other again?]
Then when will we see each other again?
Someday...
[Someday...]
Goodbye!
Director.
Director?
[Director?]
Di-
[Di?]
rec-
[rec?]
tor.
[tor?]
Would you like to order?
Sir?
S-Sir,
you can't take that!
Why do I run into him everywhere?
Hello,
I'm at your door.
I'll be right out with the kimchi.
Kimchi.
What's going on?
Why are you here?
So,
the pet sitter
who helped clean up last time
and cooked for me
was you, right?
Yes,
it was me.
Gently.
Oh.
I-It's pretty good.
N-Not good at all.
Thank... Thank god you said it's not good.
Why have you been
avoiding me?
-I didn't—
-You won't admit it.
But you ran away when you saw me
in the cafe, the convenience store,
and on the street.
I think there's a reason
for what you said that day
and why you've been avoiding me.
Close?
Weren't you just fooling around with me?
Tell me when you want to.
I'm always ready to listen.
Eden,
do you really remember nothing?
Remember nothing...
Director!
Yes?
Help me run the lines.
It's really hard to get the emotions right
practicing lines alone.
Which part?
Act 2, Scene 4.
Eden,
do you really remember nothing?
We seem to be meeting for the first time.
Have we met before?
We agreed
to go see the sea together
when we reunite.
Power outage this suddenly?
I'll go check and be right back.
Don't go.
Don't leave me alone.
Sit down!
I won't open the door for you
until you memorize it all.
Got it?
I envy Luka.
He gets to see a sea like this every day.
He gave up this precious sea
to see Eden.
So stupid.
Is it stupid to do so?
Eden doesn't remember him at all.
But for a single promise,
he gave up everything to come.
In that case,
I'm stupid too.
What do you mean?
We agreed to stand on stage together.
Because of our promise,
I've persevered until now.
I've had countless moments
wanting to give up.
Hey, it's pretty dangerous.
Let's go down.
Come up and see.
Standing here
feels like entering another world.
The hand you held mine with
was so warm
that I can never forget it.
It helped me stand up again.
You don't remember, do you?
I remember.
I've been waiting for you.
[Epilogue]
Ah, so tired.
What's going on?
Why is he sleeping here again?
Instead of going home.
I was going to sleep comfortably alone.
Oh, so sleepy.